Brandon Bisceglia

LinkedIn | Personal Site | GitHub

Email: bbisceglia10@gmail.com

Location: Pittsburgh, PA

IT Professional with 2+ years of experience in the autonomous vehicle industry, looking to translate the skills and knowledge I have gained into a new role. Highly adaptable and dedicated while also being equipped with a record of success in consistently identifying and addressing technical flaws to improve the efficiency of the product at hand.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS, Python

Technologies : Express, Node.js, Axios, Mongoose, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Mapbox, Chart.JS, MongoDB, SQLite

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ Idea, Git

EXPERIENCE

Simulation Operator

Aug 2022 – Oct 2022

Argo Al Pittsburgh, PA

• Quickly onboarded with new team and finished training 40% quicker than other peers.

• Created and enhanced simulation scenarios for the autonomous vehicles' self-driving system (SDS) software to be tested against. While simultaneously communicating between the software developers, test engineers, and team leadership to ensure desired goals are achieved.

Triage AnalystArgo AI

Aug 2020 – Aug 2022

Pittsburgh, PA

- Identified and diagnosed issues within the autonomous vehicles' self-driving system (SDS) while maintaining a
 Quality-Assurance rate above 90%.
- Collaborated on four different pilot programs for the company. Requiring me to investigate any flaws present with the SDS for that particular pilot, then organize and document my findings to key stakeholders for their assessment.
- One out of four team members appointed by direct supervisors to help facilitate training for all new employees. Which ranged from assisting with onboarding to demonstrating the team's expectations for daily tasks.

InternshipMay 2019 – Aug 2019Allegheny Health NetworkPittsburgh, PA

- I was selected as the first solo intern in the IT Department as part of a pilot program. I provided feedback and voiced my opinion on how the program could be improved to provide a pathway for developing future internship programs.
- Worked on enhancing the Epic Electronic Health Record system reporting library to make it more user-friendly and comprehensible for all its customers. By primarily using SQL and database analysis, I achieved roughly a 65% removal of reports that were either no longer being used or had been duplicated.

EDUCATION

University of Pittsburgh

Pittsburgh, PA

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Aug 2016 – April 2020

Minor - Bosnian, Croatian, Serbian Language

Pitt iServe Volunteering

The Web Developer Bootcamp

Udemy.com

PROJECTS

YelpCamp

Node.js, Express, JavaScript, Git, Bootstrap, MongoDB

Source Code

- A CRUD application exposed using RESTful routes, made with Node. is that mimics Airbnb, but for Campsites
- · Created and served the application through Express, while styling and maintaining responsiveness with Bootstrap
- Storing all data within a MongDB database, including maintaining proper encryption for user ids and passwords